freeonlineusers.com 2014-12-21

# Free Online Users - Online Users Counter

  |  |   
---  
| 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This privacy policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information collected by  www.freeonlineusers.com through our website

  * This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that  www.freeonlineusers.com does not own or control, or of persons that  www.freeonlineusers.com does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which  www.freeonlineusers.com websites link.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

  * You can visit the websites of  [ www.freeonlineusers.com](http://www.freeonlineusers.com/) without revealing any personal information. However,  www.freeonlineusers.com needs certain personal information if you wish to register for or purchase our products, register for an affiliate account, receive  www.freeonlineusers.com newsletter, or use certain  www.freeonlineusers.com services.

  * Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information.  www.freeonlineusers.com will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member.s account, and to contact you regarding new products and services.

  * By accessing the services of  www.freeonlineusers.com and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

  * www.freeonlineusers.com automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested.  www.freeonlineusers.com may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However,  www.freeonlineusers.com does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

  * www.freeonlineusers.com also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and www.freeonlineusers.com assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * www.freeonlineusers.com will not share, sell, rent or disclose your personal information to third parties unless  www.freeonlineusers.com received your written agreement to do so, this informaton would then be passed to third parties who work on behalf of www.freeonlineusers.com to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties but they are now allowed to share, sell, rent or disclose your personal information and they are required respect to personal information

  * www.freeonlineusers.com may otherwise disclose your personal information when:

  * We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;

  * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;

  * We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of www.freeonlineusers.com

  * We find that your actions on our websites violate the www.freeonlineusers.comTerms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Display Advertising**

  * www.freeonlineusers.com has implemented Display Advertising and uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. It means that third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet.

  * www.freeonlineusers.com along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

  * If you want to opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, just customize Google Display Network ads using the [ _Ads Settings_](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)  or using [ _Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on_](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)  that will instruct the Google Analytics JavaScript not to send any information about the website visit to Google Analytics.

**Consent**

  * If you do not consent to the collection or use of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to www.freeonlineusers.com. If you have provided personal information to www.freeonlineusers.comand no longer consent to its use as outlined herein, please notify us.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * www.freeonlineusers.com may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of  www.freeonlineusers.com websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

**Questions or Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at webmaster@freeonlineusers.com

|   
|  |
